You're not screwing
with me, are you?
Mr. Vincent,
I'm dead serious.
As long as you're willing to join us and
give us your loyalty,
salary's not a problem.
Yes, yes, I'll
take the position.
Besides, the Eagles,
they just fired me.
That's the dumbest thing they've ever done.
Don't worry, Mr. Vincent.
My team is going
to treat you
with the respect
you deserve.
Thanks so much.
Great.
Looking forward to it.
Yes!
Ted Vincent is joining us as head coach.
And...
I am adding him to our player roster.
Just in case.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why are you registering him as a player?
Isn't he supposed to be our new head coach?
Plus, he's old.
Okay, do you remember about 10 years ago,
there was a
college quarterback
who was phenomenal...
All-American...
His name was Ted.
Of course.
He broke his leg during the championship.
If that hadn't happened,
he'd have been a superstar by now.
Hold on, sis.
You're saying
he's that Ted?
Yes, sis.
I've already had him checked out thoroughly.
With him on our side,
we're definitely winning the championship.
Boo!
Hey, buddy.
You know what NFL stands for?
Not for long.
That's how long
you'll be coaching.
Three close games
in a row?
Really?
This is the worst team
in the division.
There's no reason for it
to be this close.
I'll fuck your cousin!
Fuck, poor fucker.
What the hell happened?
You lost to a
third-rate team?
You were winning
so easy before.
They must have studied our plays.
Every route
was locked down.
We won't lose again.
When Ted was here,
he always changed our plays on the fly.
We never struggled
like this.
If he were here today,
we wouldn't have lost.
Shut the fuck up, James.
Ted?
You mean that assistant who led victory last time?